Pick out some bread and drinks for breakfast tomorrow.
Right!
Do it without running!
He doesn't listen to a thing I say.
Let's see. For a cold, we need water,
sports drinks, dairy products,
and some food that's easy to digest.
Want to get something for breakfast, Rin?
Like cereal or something?
Yes.
Daikichi...
Did I give it to her?
You...
The cold virus is everywhere.
Sometimes you catch it, and sometimes you don't.
You don't have to worry about where she caught it.
Can I pick out something to give her too?
Sure.
This!
Put it in here.
Kouki-kun.
And what exactly are you doing in the snacks corner?
Kouki! About breakfast-
It came off!
My place is this way!
Actually, I think we should leave.
I don't want to bother her.
Okay.
There's food in here. Give it to your mom.
It's heavy.
Whoa, that's heavy!
Let's go, Rin.
Mom! Daikichi gave us stuff to eat!
Didn't you hear what I just said?
Kouki!
Daikichi-san...
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble!
N-No, we owe you for when you took care of Rin.
How's Rin-chan?
She's completely fine.
She went to school today too.
Good evening.
Good evening. Glad you're all right, Rin-chan.
I'm making that porridge right now.
I'll be feeling better in no time.
Rin, let's go throw my tooth.
This way!
Be careful, Kouki.
Yeah.
Nitani-san, you might have gotten your cold from Rin.
I'm sorry.
I'll throw it from here!
I meet a lot of people every day.
Wow!
I take a crowded train to work.
There's no telling where I got it from,
so don't worry about it.
It's just a cold.
I understand.
The least I could do is help out with Kouki.
I could pick him up.
Thank you.
Rin, let's go home.
Daikichi, let's play video games.
Yeah, some other time.
Kouki, make sure you help your mom out.
Okay!
That's right.
The pudding and small drink are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Pudding is my favorite!
Good night.
Daikichi! Hurry up!
It's still early, and it's Sunday.
I told you I have practice for the jump rope competition.
What's wrong?
This one is wobbling too.
Brush softly.
Okay.
Don't touch it!
Ouch!
Is it okay for you to be up?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry for taking advantage of your kindness.
Me too. Thank you very much.
Not at all.
I'm a little surprised at Kouki.
He can't seem to do it at all.
Kouki, you're jumping too soon.
The rope comes around like this, and you have to jump here, right?
Yeah.
So you shouldn't move your arms and legs at the same time.
I see.
First your arms, then your legs.
Try doing it slowly first.
Okay!
Daikichi! Me too, me too!
Yeah, yeah.
Rin, you swing your arms too wide.
Keep your arms close, like this.
Daikichi-san!
You're pretty early!
Good morning!
They're sure in high spirits.
Nobu-kun is pretty good.
It's because of his big brother.
He copies him.
Sayaka-chan, aren't you going to join them?
One of her upper teeth came off.
Girls have it rough even when they're small.
Sayaka-chan.
What kind of container do you have for your teeth?
Do you have a cute one?
What's that?
A case to store the baby teeth as a keepsake.
You don't know?
Keepsake?
They have these small and cute ones.
Small?
Cute?
Right?
Yes.
Mine's a butterfly!
I bought one for my kid too.
Sounds like something Rin would love!
Dammit! To think there'd be things like that!
It's always been like this since I met Rin.
I get all flustered and scared over the smallest things.
Kaga Rin
Daikichi
The meat and potatoes that
Daikichi make are very tasty.
Also, Daikichi can
run fast.
Daikichi, you can have this!
I drew it at school.
We were supposed to introduce someone from our home.
Oh, well.
It's so cute!
What is it?
You put your baby teeth in there
as a keepsake.
Keepsake?
Thank you, Kouki-kun's mom!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's?
It's fine.
I'll throw mine with all my strength!
As you can see.
I already threw the other ones up until now.
Is that okay?
Sure it is. You can keep some and throw some. It'll be fine.
I see.
Rin, I'll jump rope with you next time!
There you go, touching it again.
Just leave it be. It'll came off soon enough.
She'll definitely look like she got punched.
She should at least keep herself from smiling.
Okay, done.
Let's go!
Did you grow taller again?
Huh? Daikichi-san too?
I'm gaining a bit here.
Same here.
It's tough once you reach this age.
I want to hold it back, somehow.
Daikichi-san is doing it like a boxer!
Awesome!
It's easier on the knees this way.
Daikichi, show me how to do that!
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
No way!
What, you want to be the only cool one?
You need to be able to jump properly first!
What did you say?
Wait up!
Me too!
Rin-chan, you're so good at skipping backwards!
Kids are amazing.
Kids are full of energy.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Why do they have so much stamina?
Well, adults are amazing too.
Adults?
I'm sure you guys know about it too.
I'm not Rin's dad. We just started living together a year ago.
Until then, I just spent all my time for myself.
After I started living with Rin, my lifestyle suddenly changed.
But you guys have been with kids for a long time now.
It's still early for me, so I'm fine.
I'm just wondering if I can live without any time for myself in the future.
I don't think that way at all.
Me neither.
Is that so?
Well, that's obvious.
What is?
Rin, didn't you have the jump rope competition today?
Yeah.
Rin...
I messed up.
How many jumps?
15.
That's horrible!
What about backwards?
203 times.
You jumped that many times?
Did you get first place for that?
Yes. This is the certificate.
Certificate of Merit
First Year
Backward Skipping Competition 1st Place
Kaga Rin
You really worked hard.
This is great.
I could have done more in the forward jumping, though.
You only get one chance, don't you?
Besides, you can jump a lot now.
I know that for a fact.
I lost some weight!
Huh?
Hey!
Will we be there soon?
Yeah, around 10 minutes.
They want to look at your wobbly front teeth.
Come on, don't keep touching them.
I want to show them how good I can jump rope.
Sure.
You've grown a lot lately.
I'm sure my mom and dad will be surprised.
I wonder if she'll say that I'll outgrow her soon.
It's too early for that.
I need to report this to Grandpa too.
We're here!
Rin-chan, I was waiting to see you.
I'm home.
Oh, you've gotten so big.
Are you one of the tallest in the class?
Yes!
You should've called us. We would've come to pick you up by car.
It's just 10 minutes, and Rin wanted to walk.
You'll outgrow me soon.
Kazumi-onee-chan!
Hey there. You're here pretty early.
Yeah, I just got in.
Those clothes...
You used to wear them, right?
Yeah.
Your mom sent them over the other day.
Rin-chan, let me look at your teeth.
Okay!
The two front teeth are wobbling now.
Are you okay? Doesn't it hurt?
Sometimes, but I'm used to it.
I'm a pro after all!
Daikichi! Can't we do something for her?
Her gums are getting red!
They're just a little red.
Besides, you wanted to tie strings to mine and pull them out!
A string?!
Oh, did I?
I made it all as soft as possible.
Thank you!
You want some tofu?
Yeah.
Can I have some boiled beans too?
Sure!
Eat as much as you like.
I love tofu!
Did it come off?
Rin-chan?
It came off!
She's bleeding!
Mom, the tissues!
Just a minute!
I'm fine!
Rin, use this for now!
That's a cleaning cloth!
Rin-chan has changed a lot.
I wonder about that.
That might be the real Rin.
I hear you're getting married.
Mom told me earlier.
Yeah.
That's great.
I heard he's a good guy.
I guess.
Only thing is, he wants a kid as soon as possible.
That's nice.
No, it isn't!
Drinking, going to concerts,
taking trips, eating tasty food...
I won't be able to do any of that!
You should talk about it with him.
I don't get it.
Besides, I'm horrible with kids.
I don't want to become a whiny old lady either!
I don't think I can sacrifice myself to take care of a kid.
No, it'll all work out.
If that's what you decide,
you won't have a choice.
You're talking like this doesn't concern you.
Well, that might be true.
What's that supposed to mean?
I've never had to be in the position of a mother, father, or husband.
It's burning.
It's true I don't have time to shop leisurely
or go out for tea,
but when I'm working, that time is for me alone.
The time I spend with my child is my time too,
and it's very precious.
Being a parent isn't anything special.
There are moms and dads everywhere you look.
I see.
That's true.
Grandpa, you know what?
My adult teeth are starting to grow in.
Hey, Rin!
I-It's just sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry up!
I'm taking it!
That jar...
Masako-san had one too.
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What? Another one's coming off?
I need a mirror!
I'll probably continue getting flustered over small things from here on out.
That's probably true for a lot of people.
Does is hurt?
Rin?
Daikichi, look at this!
Hey, you look like a cat.
Right?
Mail something to your house!
A picture?
In any case,
Yes!
I think that smile will turn into my own happiness.
Hurry up!
Okay, open your mouth.
And I think things are just fine the way they are.
Daikichi!